I want you to take a look at this
unfinished graph the top line is the
data for women from 1998 to 2022 and the
bottom line is the data for men from the
same time period without explaining
anything more could you guess what this
graph represents I'll give you a second
to think about it if you guessed that
this graph shows the difference between
how many times men and women piss while
sitting down per day you're wrong it
actually shows the percentage of men and
women between the ages of 19 to 28 who
identify as liberal for almost two
decades these numbers remained
relatively stable with about 30% of both
men and women identifying as liberal but
around 2015 that started to change
drastically I think this graph is the
perfect visual representation of not
only the growing disparity of political
ideologies between men and women but the
overall disagreeableness between men and
women in modern society as well while I
am definitely no gender studies expert I
am something that a small demographic of
the internet deems important a random
guy online with an opinion so let me
bring up my main quarrels with the
current online gender war that is now
slowly seeping its way into reality and
what I think we should do moving forward
how does one accurately Define their
role in society for the past thousand
years or so ever since large scale
civilization spawned the answer to this
question has relatively remained the
same at least for most societies men are
the providers they get the high-paying
jobs do the difficult physical work and
make sure their family is safe women on
the other hand nurture they usually only
stay at home care for the kids and do
all the other stuff we traditionally
associated with what women should do but
now those distinctions have gotten
pretty confusing the laws that were put
into place to prevent women from
reaching the same sort of Financial
Security without needing a husband to do
the working for them are virtually
non-existent the amount of jobs that
don't require intense physical labor and
the value of these jobs is also
skyrocketed as well such as jobs in the
tech industry and as a result women can
choose to be single own a house and make
just as much if not more money than if
they were to to have a partner this has
given women far more power and influence
over their own lives as well as the
society that they're in and I believe
that this is the root cause of all the
problems we're now seeing Sprout up
between men and women that can sound
like I'm saying that women having more
autonomy over their lives is a bad thing
so before you put words into my mouth
let me just clear up that that's not
what I'm saying at all I need to
continue explaining if you ask any young
man what being a man means the answer is
not going to be a straight cut as it
once was and a large part of the reason
as to why this is is because there has
been a push back on traditional
masculinity with less father figures in
real life more time spent online and
loads of information on why masculinity
is damaging to both men and women young
men just don't know how they're supposed
to act especially when it comes to
interacting with women a lot of the
social importance has been heavily
favored towards empowering women in
recent years and it's left a lot of
dudes feeling like they are
underappreciated or undervalued for what
they do neither gender is exclusively at
fault here on the one hand you have a
lot of men within red pill spaces
pushing the narrative that marriage and
getting into a serious relationship with
just one woman is not worth it anymore
that modern women are delusional and
that marriage is heavily skewed in a
woman's favor so this deters young men
from pursuing the traditional part of
masculinity related to being a provider
for a family and I know that a lot of
these red pill guys are not
intentionally trying to demotivate you
but when you tell men that they should
just say screw it to marriage and do all
the work that they're doing for
themselves and for themselves only I
think this leaves a lot of guys feeling
empty like all their work is for nothing
because in the end it won't even be
appreciated these types of narratives
pushed by hardcore red pillars also
completely skew the perception of how
women think and act but we'll get to
that later in the video then on the
other hand we have all of these large
media sources giving positive
masculinity no attention and trying to
empower women and have them be more
represented as workingclass citizens who
are capable of just as much as men are
which side note I don't think is a bad
thing on its own but then we also have
women spreading the idea that men are
not needed anymore and if you really do
want a man then you should wait for the
absolute perfect one to come into your
life so it's this really destructive
cycle of men feeling like they have no
reason to improve which makes the
quality of Great Men Who qualify for
relationships decrease and on top of
that women are raising their standards
for what they will tolerate with a man
because they now have the power to do so
but simultaneously Wonder why there
aren't more men who fit the bill not
realizing that it's this I don't need a
man mentality that leads to their being
less great men in the first place and
the men who are now not fitting the bill
who in the past might have had a much
greater chance of finding a relationship
or a marriage with a woman because she
needed to get married to get her basic
needs met are outraged with this new way
of living the more that women embrace
the choice we have and who we want as a
partner the more it terrifies the the
males who fear they won't be chosen just
follow me here okay the more that women
exercise their right to choose the kind
of partner they want or if they even
want a partner at all the more it
terrifies the males who know they don't
fit the bill physically socially and or
financially cuz most males I would argue
are mediocre and are lacking a lot of
important qualities you need to have a
successful partnership but back in the
day baby that did not matter mediocre
males were still being chosen out of our
need to survive now that we are in a
time where we no longer need males for
us to meet our basic needs need a
survival mediocre males are being left
behind in droves I'm not going to lie
this woman is spitting some truth here
and the usual Resort for men who no
longer meet that standard is to sadly
turn to the red pill and the manosphere
and take out all their frustrations by
calling women hypergamous hoes but
there's a comment I want to bring up
underneath this video that will lead us
to the next place I want to go with this
this woman said going to be a whole lot
more single lonely men in our future but
they brought that on themselves did did
they really bring that on themselves
though did young men create the society
we currently live in or was that past
older Generations fact of the matter is
the young men that are actually being
punished for this had absolutely no say
in the matter and did not benefit from
society being the way it was in previous
generations and this is a massive
problem I see with both genders there's
a complete lack of empathy when either
side tries to make a valid criticism
about the opposite sex here's a crazy
fact 55% of single men aged 18 to 30 say
they haven't approached a woman in the
past year but 77% of women aged 18 to 30
say they wished they were approached
more and 86% of women say they want the
man to make the first move seems like
exclusively a male problem right why
don't men just approach more then well
problem is 82% of women reported
experiencing creepy Behavior sometimes
often or constantly and 50% of men
report not wanting to approach women for
fear of being seen as creepy or
predatory as podcast and friend Chris
Williamson put it women face a dilemma
they are scared for their safety but
also have a preference for men making
the first move men face a dilemma they
are terrified of being seen as creepy
but also know that if they don't
approach a woman the conversation is
unlikely to start but I believe a big
reason that wasn't brought up as to why
men are now more afraid to approach
women is because of what I stated
earlier that demonization of masculinity
and particularly being assertive when
you are trying to approach a woman and
you're trying to get a date the odds of
a false allegation ruining your life and
having the entire world see is much
greater thanks to the internet and I'm
not going to sit here and say that more
men getting exposed is doing only harm
because obviously it's not these men who
may have gotten away scott-free in the
past who are terribly abusive and
assault women are now getting exposed
for who they truly are and that's
awesome but the line between being
creepy and harassing a woman or simply
just flirting with her and trying to get
her number is a bit more confusing now
due to the fact that so many men have
been falsely accused of harassment or
assault and have had their entire lives
ruined the last data point I left out
from the earlier findings is that 177%
of Americans aged 18 to 29 believe that
a man inviting a woman out for a drink
always or usually constitutes sa that is
a pretty significant number often times
the same women who are bashing men for
being so docile insecure and weird are
the same ones who wish they got
approached more not realizing that the
media has portrayed men approaching
women in a very bad light in recent
years but once again it's not like men
are innocent for one yeah women women
are scary I get it but you can be ahead
of 55% of men if you simply just go up
to a woman and actually ask her out on a
date 55% of men aren't willing to do
that or haven't done that there's one
more real example I want to use to
highlight the lack of sympathy between
both genders this dude made a real about
not wanting to pursue a 10 out of 10
looking woman because they look too
expensive and he knew they would be too
much work and besides the real in and of
itself that you could easily generate an
opinion on the comments below are just
men and women non-stop back and forth
roasting each other with women saying
men need to know their place and stop
being broke and dudes attacking the
physical appearance of all the women in
the comments who have anything to say
about it absolutely nothing was gained
from this post and it only made a bunch
of men and women mad at each other for
not meeting each other's expectations
you know what these people probably need
more than anything therapy and maybe
online therapy using today's sponsor
better help relationships with the
opposite sex are very tricky especially
when you don't have help from a
professional outside of you and I know
in my past experience I've used therapy
and it has helped a lot with kind of
clearing up my mind regarding
relationships with women and with better
help it makes therapy a lot easier to
get into and less intimidating for many
people better help lets you have therapy
sessions as a phone call a video chat or
even messaging whatever is the most
comfortable version of therapy for you
all you do is fill out a questionnaire
that will ask you questions about what
challenges you're going through and what
kind of therapists you like and then
they will match you to one of their over
30,000 therapists in their network based
on your needs preferences and location
you'll be matched with a therapist in
most cases within 48 hours and the great
part about better help that sets it from
therapy in person is that because they
have such a big network of therapists if
you find you aren't vibing with your
therapist aren't helping you it is free
and easy to switch your therapist at any
time so you can join 4 million people
who have used better help to live a
happier healthier life if you go to my
link betterhelp.com that is
betterhelp.com and you're going to get
10% off your first month of therapy if
you use that link now let's talk about
the absolutely ludicrous expectations
that both men and women have for the
opposite gender I'd like to ask all of
the young hetero people watching this
video a question how much of your time
spent in a day consuming conversations
of the opposite sex is from the internet
and how much of your conversations with
the opposite sex are from real life I
can only imagine that for a lot of you
at least half of your social interaction
is coming from social media and here I
am about to go over something that needs
to be brought up once again for men in
terms of how the online World influences
their perception of women I've noticed
that there's two opposing sides to it
first there's this Rabbit Hole of only a
certain type of woman highlighted on
social media that they get sucked into
like I shared earlier because many young
men don't have any sort of Father Figure
or role model in their lives and at the
same time are being taught that their
masculine traits are wrong they usually
get sucked into The Men Who stand out
the most when it comes to fighting back
against these sorts of ideas and the men
who stand out the most due to the fact
that they post the most controversial
polarizing takes are usually the red
pill content creators there are
obviously big issues isues with this the
only type of women you will usually see
on their podcasts are the ones who are
either uneducated have only fans they're
trying to promote or both and this
creates the idea in young impressionable
guys mind that this must be how most
women are thinking and acting ladies
please name three countries we haven't
done this one in a while we'll start
right here with Miss red Africa
Tennessee Tennessee I don't know that's
they bring on these types of women
specifically because number one it's
easier for the host to gain control over
the conversation and dominate the
podcast without a strong rebuttal and
two these types of women usually have
the most polarizing takes like I was
talking about earlier and that makes for
good entertainment have you seen what
happens when a woman with good critical
thinking skills who's not afraid to
speak up for themselves actually makes
it on one of these shows I'll show you
if you have only one place in your heart
for one woman or you want to have one
woman in your heart I think you said why
don't you just commit to one and choose
to be faithful to her I'm just not a
wired that way I spent my whole 20s
trying to fix myself thought you're a
man of selfcontrol you you work out you
do business you can possess your own
your own power and direct it the way you
want not how I am it's not how I am you
think that might be a limited mindset I
think it's none of your business but I
don't want you to think I'm triggered by
you I'm not okay I saw somebody say that
and I think that's interesting I think
you're annoying but I'm not triggered
you know what I'm saying no you are
you're annoying in like this goody two
shoes type way and that's fine this dude
just completely projected and her answer
obviously made him a little insecure I
bet she doesn't get invited back to one
of these podcasts again and then there's
all these viral clips of garbage Street
interviews that again only highlight
very promiscuous Unfaithful women I'm
single as of yesterday you had a man
before yesterday for 2 years not going
to lie I got a appointment coming with
who my best friend you were friends with
this guy while you were dating your your
boyfriend I've been friends with him
before I knew my ex I guess now this is
the type of that men are getting
fed ridiculous
then on the other opposing side as to
how social media has influenced men's
perception of women is the completely
unrealistic standards they have for
women and how attractive they should be
at least physically remember that reel I
showed you about the dude not trying to
entertain a 10 out of 10 well there are
plenty of conventionally objectively
attractive women in the comments and a
bunch of dudes replying to their
comments saying you're a four out of 10
anyways and you have to wear tons of
makeup when the woman is completely out
of their leak now they could actually
think that woman is very attractive and
they're just saying that in order to
appear cool in the comments to other men
but I genuinely think that a lot of
these guys think women are supposed to
look the way they do when they put on
Snapchat filters and Instagram filters
hell I just saw a dude on Twitter talk
about how Sydney Sweeney was a 5.5 out
of 10 in Europe and a three out of 10
not even noticeable on the Metro in
Russia I don't know how true that is but
are you guys serious with these
standards and what you think you can get
I see loads of dudes online commenting
stuff like at this point with the way
that the dating Market is I would take a
girl who looks like a dumpster but your
dumpster is a woman with an insane body
and a stunning face you're ridding
yourself of the opportunity of meeting a
genuinely amazing woman because your
standards are built on Tik Tok and
Instagram models and you only focus on
physical appearance it's crazy but
luckily from what I've seen this really
only applies to chronically online men
now as for women and their expectations
we already know where this goes dating
apps are 80% men 20% women and this is
how the majority of young people meet
now 20% of women can choose from the
very top percentage attractiveness of
these dating apps as a result women can
make their own money and be their own
person without a man and therefore what
you need to be doing as a man for a lot
of woman is to be truly exceptional in
all aspects of Life the fact of the
matter is unlike chronically online men
who have these really high expectations
that are aren't at all congruent with
their own charm and Charisma most women
actually do have the option to choose
the best option it's pretty congruent
with the death of the middle class in
America like the rich get richer poor
get poorer Concepts which is happening a
lot of men as an argument like to say oh
if you keep up these standards you're
going to be single when you're 40 and
you're going to be wondering where have
all the good men gone and you're going
to wish that you never held out that
long but I honestly think that yes some
of these women are going to wish that
they didn't hold out for this perfect
man that may have never existed or that
may not be at the same standards as they
think they are but a lot of these women
are not going to care that they're
single and that's partly due to the fact
that they're being fed the narrative
that men aren't needed anymore and like
we saw earlier that infuriates men who
don't fit that standard but like I
stated a lot of this stuff only exists
on the internet at least for now it's
actually wild to me how many below
average looking dudes I walk by on a
daily basis who have girlfriends simply
because they have something going for
them they're friendly romantic and
confident and they actually approach
women in real life and that leads me to
ask how do we stop the NeverEnding
constant battle between men and women
that is now only Amplified in the
digital age well I don't know I'm just
some random guy on the internet but
maybe we can start with realizing that
both men and women struggle both men and
women have issues in double standards
they have to deal with and maybe if we
hold ourselves to high but realistic
standards then we can stop feeling such
a disconnect between each other men and
women will always be different in the
way each of us function and what makes
us happy in both platonic and romantic
relationships and if you don't
understand this difference and know how
to calmly communicate it in a way where
you're not just projecting getting
defensive angry and just personally
attacking someone that's when actual
progress in understanding one another is
made to me that starts with encouraging
proper parenting having a two parent
household lowers the risk of poverty
prison and increases the rate of
pursuing a higher education but it also
means that your son or daughter has the
opportunity to get perspectives from
both a man and a woman's side the future
of society will be shaped by the people
that children look up to and ideally
those people for men wouldn't be the
people that are being pushed out by the
manosphere and for women wouldn't be I
don't know what's the female equivalent
of the manosphere spere women who say
men are useless and trash yeah basically
any sort of role model that lacks
respect for the opposite gender and
speaks badly of them because they don't
realize that they're projecting their
past experiences with shitty men or
women onto others please stop with this
whole men are trash women are trash
narrative men and women have their own
unique strengths and weaknesses and
maybe you don't want to admit it but we
do need each other and that needing each
other should come from a place where we
should be treated treated equally where
it makes sense to be treated equally and
not push this narrative that femininity
is toxic or masculinity is toxic because
both masculine and feminine energies
when people actually do the work to heal
and have a high emotional IQ are
beautiful expressions of Life men
instead of roasting and constantly
bashing a dude for having emotions or
being down bad or spending a ton of Time
online complaining about the standards
of women while not actually doing
anything to change yourself let's start
directing our energy towards lifting
each other up Men's education and drive
and purpose is at what seems to be an
all-time low and although women have
raised their standards and are really
Holding Out for that exceptional man it
is much easier to stand out now and be
that exceptional man if you have a
purpose that you're working towards and
you're really working on yourself a lot
of y'all men are really convinced thanks
to the internet that if you ask a girl
out she's going to consider you a sex
offender or something like that but what
I see in real life life 95% of the time
if you are asking her out like they're
not going to think you're creepy and
please stop taking advice on how to
treat women from the guy who has never
had a successful marriage and treats
women like dispensable objects now women
realize that men being men and being
strong and secure in their masculine
energy does not at all take away from
the power that you have more healthy
outlets for men to be men need to be
pushed by not only other men on the
internet but women as well the issues
that men are having right now are very
real and much of the media is against
masculinity so just like how strong men
will listen to you and listen to your
issues you should be open and receptive
to listening and understanding what men
are trying to say right now and to both
men and women stop getting your
perception of how men and women are
based on how you see men and women
online and stop assuming the worst when
you do interact with men or women in
real life just because of of what you
saw online before consuming a piece of
media and getting mad at it ask yourself
is this accurately portraying how
experiences between men and women go
every day in real life and are these
conversations generating ideas that will
contribute to the positive cooperation
of men and women in a postmodern world
where gender roles are less defined you
can usually find the answers to these
questions based on the ratio of healthy
to destructive conversations that are
happening in the comment section but
what all of these Solutions come from is
having more accountabil
more understanding and more inner work
being done from both sides there are
plenty of incredible men and women that
are pushing positive healthy versions of
masculinity and femininity but the
problem is their voices rarely get
Amplified because they aren't generating
a ton of Engagement so if you ever see
that please like and share the out
of it heal from whatever man or woman
Did You Wrong and if you want to be
understood try to First understand why
the other side has the thoughts and
feelings that they do now you're still
going to meet plenty of of insecure
unwilling to understand men or women
when you try to do this and that's fine
the real problem arises when you let
that grow anger hatred or annoyance
within
you so I haven't announced this on video
yet but I've actually created a free
self-improvement community for both men
and women or whatever you identify as
and that is one of the first links in my
description below if you want to join a
free self-improvement community and have
meaningful conversations where people
are open-minded did and are actually
generating positive beneficial
discussions then check that link in my
description and yeah join that free
community it's fun I'm so excited to see
all of the irony in the comments I'm
sure it's going to be really civil down
there maybe you want to go check it out
grab some popcorn but if you want to
watch another video like this one where
I talk about the masculinity crisis in
more detail check out this video right
here and I'm heading out thank you for
watching thank you for listening and I
love you guys peace